[{"Date": "2020-07-24 14:41:32+00:00", "question": "[20/20] Reading skill can be developed best by", "option1": "Writing answer to questions on text", "option2": "Focusing on the use of word from context to text", "option3": "Doing vocabulary exercises", "option4": "Doing quizees and playing word game", "Answer": "Focusing on the use of word from context to text"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:41:00+00:00", "question": "[19/20] Select the word which means the same as the group of words given.\n\nAn underground hole dug by a small animal as a dwelling", "option1": "Drain", "option2": "Pit", "option3": "Cave", "option4": "Burrow", "Answer": "Burrow"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:40:28+00:00", "question": "[18/20] Meena is eight years old girl. She does not like to study. You as a teacher:", "option1": "Give her oral work", "option2": "Leaves on her own in the class", "option3": "Request how to study despite she is not interested", "option4": "Describe the benefit of study", "Answer": "Describe the benefit of study"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:39:57+00:00", "question": "[17/20] Select the most appropriate antonym of the given word.\n\nINFERIOR", "option1": "Ulterior", "option2": "Exterior", "option3": "Interior", "option4": "Superior", "Answer": "Superior"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:39:25+00:00", "question": "[16/20] Select the word which means the same as the group of words given.\n\nOne who eats too much", "option1": "Overweight", "option2": "Glutton", "option3": "Corpulent", "option4": "Obese", "Answer": "Glutton"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:38:53+00:00", "question": "[15/20] When reading is done to 'encode', it means to", "option1": "Gathering relevant information", "option2": "Convert graphic medium to the visual medium or vice versa", "option3": "Hide additional meaning in communication", "option4": "Express meaning in different formats", "Answer": "Express meaning in different formats"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:38:21+00:00", "question": "[14/20] In learning a new language, multilingualism\u00a0", "option1": "An assets", "option2": "An interference", "option3": "A burden", "option4": "A methodology", "Answer": "An assets"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:37:49+00:00", "question": "[13/20] Proper speech habits can be developed effectively through", "option1": "Vocabulary practice", "option2": "Quizzes", "option3": "Dictations", "option4": "Pronunciation", "Answer": "Pronunciation"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:37:18+00:00", "question": "[12/20] Which of the following is NOT an essential qualities of a good teacher?", "option1": "Ability to build relationships with students", "option2": "Patient, kind and caring personality", "option3": "Dedicated to learning", "option4": "None of these", "Answer": "None of these"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:36:46+00:00", "question": "[11/20] When a teacher enters his class on the first day the theme of discussion should be :", "option1": "School building", "option2": "School principal", "option3": "Course-content", "option4": "Introduction", "Answer": "Introduction"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:36:14+00:00", "question": "[10/20] Select the most appropriate synonym of the given word.\n\nERODE", "option1": "Fix", "option2": "Disintegrate", "option3": "Preserve", "option4": "Build", "Answer": "Disintegrate"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:35:42+00:00", "question": "[9/20] The process of word formation consists of", "option1": "Compounding and /affixes", "option2": "Opposite and meaning", "option3": "Verbs and noun", "option4": "Using synonyms of euphemism", "Answer": "Compounding and /affixes"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:35:10+00:00", "question": "[8/20] Fill in the blanks.\nGandhiji had ____________ the path of non-violence", "option1": "Suggested", "option2": "Accepted", "option3": "Adopted", "option4": "Proposed", "Answer": "Adopted"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:34:38+00:00", "question": "[7/20] He is poor\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026he is satisfied with his situation.", "option1": "Yet", "option2": "So", "option3": "But", "option4": "While", "Answer": "Yet"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:34:07+00:00", "question": "[6/20] After reading a story on fish, if a teacher asks children to answer \u2013 \u201cImagine you are a fish in a pond. What do you see around you ?\u201d This is an example of", "option1": "Cloze type questions", "option2": "Open ended questions", "option3": "Multiple choice questions", "option4": "Comprehension questions", "Answer": "Open ended questions"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:33:35+00:00", "question": "[5/20] A good text-book of English should possess", "option1": "Reading material", "option2": "Picture and illustrations", "option3": "Cultural content", "option4": "All of the above", "Answer": "All of the above"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:33:03+00:00", "question": "[4/20] Giving effective feedback to the learners means", "option1": "Diagnosing problem and guiding cullinan on how to improve", "option2": "Giving appropriate time and space for corrections", "option3": "Focus on positive expect as well as the areas of development", "option4": "Correcting the mistake in the class", "Answer": "Focus on positive expect as well as the areas of development"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:32:31+00:00", "question": "[3/20] Standardized assessment means ____ assessment.", "option1": "Formative", "option2": "Summative", "option3": "Frequent", "option4": "Alternative", "Answer": "Summative"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:31:59+00:00", "question": "[2/20] Select the most appropriate synonym of the given word\n\nSANE", "option1": "Foolish", "option2": "Crazy", "option3": "Sensitive", "option4": "Sensible", "Answer": "Sensible"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 14:31:27+00:00", "question": "[1/20] Select the word which means the same as the group of words given.\n\nA room or building with equipment for doing physical exercise", "option1": "Dormitory", "option2": "Convent", "option3": "Infirmary", "option4": "Gymnasium", "Answer": "Gymnasium"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:44:37+00:00", "question": "[8/20] Dietary intake of...... is essential for the normal functioning of thyroid gland.\n\u0925\u093e\u092f\u0930\u093e\u0907\u0921 \u0917\u094d\u0930\u0902\u0925\u093f \u0915\u0947 \u0938\u093e\u092e\u093e\u0928\u094d\u092f \u0915\u093e\u092e\u0915\u093e\u091c \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f..... \u0915\u093e \u0906\u0939\u093e\u0930 \u0938\u0947\u0935\u0928 \u0906\u0935\u0936\u094d\u092f\u0915 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Iodine", "option2": "Potassium", "option3": "Sodium", "option4": "Calcium", "Answer": "Iodine"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:44:06+00:00", "question": "[7/20] \u0935\u093e\u0938\u094d\u0924\u0935\u093f\u0915 \u0935\u0938\u094d\u0924\u0941 \u0915\u093e \u0906\u092d\u093e\u0938\u0940 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u093f\u092c\u093f\u0902\u092c \u092c\u0928\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?\u00ae", "option1": "\u0907\u0928\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902", "option2": "\u0909\u0924\u094d\u0924\u0932 \u0926\u0930\u094d\u092a\u0923 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option3": "\u0905\u0935\u0924\u0932 \u0926\u0930\u094d\u092a\u0923 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option4": "\u0938\u092e\u0924\u0932 \u0926\u0930\u094d\u092a\u0923 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "Answer": "\u0938\u092e\u0924\u0932 \u0926\u0930\u094d\u092a\u0923 \u092e\u0947\u0902"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:43:34+00:00", "question": "[6/20] Acid rain is caused by the pollution of environment by\n\u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932 \u0935\u0930\u094d\u0937\u093e \u092a\u0930\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0926\u0942\u0937\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0923 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Carbon monoxide and carbon dioxide", "option2": "Nitrous oxide and Sulphur dioxide", "option3": "Carbon dioxide and nitrogen", "option4": "Ozone and carbon dioxide", "Answer": "Nitrous oxide and Sulphur dioxide"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:43:02+00:00", "question": "[5/20] Which of the following is the form of calcium carbonate\n\u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u0915\u0948\u0932\u0936\u093f\u092f\u092e \u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092c\u094b\u0928\u0947\u091f \u0915\u093e \u090f\u0915 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Table salt", "option2": "Limestone", "option3": "Baking soda", "option4": "Washing soda", "Answer": "Limestone"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:42:30+00:00", "question": "[4/20] 'Fly-ash\" as well-known pollutant is produced by\n'\u092b\u094d\u0932\u093e\u0908- \u0910\u0936' \u0914\u0930 \u0938\u093e\u0925 \u0939\u0940 \u0938\u093e\u0925 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0926\u0942\u0937\u0915 \u0915\u0947 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u091c\u093e\u0928\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948", "option1": "Oil refinery \u0924\u0947\u0932 \u0930\u093f\u092b\u093e\u0907\u0928\u0930\u0940", "option2": "Thermal power plant \u0924\u093e\u092a \u0935\u093f\u0926\u094d\u092f\u0941\u0924 \u0938\u0902\u092f\u0902\u0924\u094d\u0930", "option3": "Cement plant \u0938\u0940\u092e\u0947\u0902\u091f \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0916\u093e\u0928\u093e", "option4": "Fertilizer plant \u0909\u0930\u094d\u0935\u0930\u0915 \u0938\u0902\u092f\u0902\u0924\u094d\u0930", "Answer": "Thermal power plant \u0924\u093e\u092a \u0935\u093f\u0926\u094d\u092f\u0941\u0924 \u0938\u0902\u092f\u0902\u0924\u094d\u0930"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:41:58+00:00", "question": "[3/20] \u092a\u094d\u0932\u0947\u0917 \u0939\u0948\nThe plague is \u00ae", "option1": "\u0916\u0928\u093f\u091c \u091c\u0928\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u0940\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0940 mineral disease", "option2": "\u0915\u0935\u0915 \u091c\u0928\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u0940\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0940 fungal disease", "option3": "\u091c\u0940\u0935\u093e\u0923\u0941 \u091c\u0928\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u0940\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0940 bacterial disease", "option4": "\u0935\u093f\u0937\u093e\u0923\u0941 \u091c\u0928\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u0940\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0940 viral disease", "Answer": "\u091c\u0940\u0935\u093e\u0923\u0941 \u091c\u0928\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u0940\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0940 bacterial disease"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:41:27+00:00", "question": "[2/20] The oxide of nitrogen which is acidic as well as paramagnetic in nature is\n\u0928\u093e\u0907\u091f\u094d\u0930\u094b\u091c\u0928 \u0915\u093e \u0911\u0915\u094d\u0938\u093e\u0907\u0921 \u091c\u094b \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932\u0940\u092f \u0939\u094b\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0938\u093e\u0925-\u0938\u093e\u0925 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u0943\u0924\u093f \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u0948\u0930\u093e\u092e\u0948\u0917\u094d\u0928\u0947\u091f\u093f\u0915 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948", "option1": "NO", "option2": "N2O5", "option3": "N2", "option4": "N20", "Answer": "NO"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 13:40:55+00:00", "question": "[1/20] what becomes speed of light with increase in medium temperature\n\u092e\u093e\u0927\u094d\u092f\u092e \u0915\u0947 \u0924\u093e\u092a\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0935\u0943\u0926\u094d\u0927\u093f \u0915\u0947 \u0938\u093e\u0925 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0915\u0940 \u0917\u0924\u093f\u00ae", "option1": "\u0905\u091a\u093e\u0928\u0915 \u0915\u092e \u0939\u094b \u091c\u093e\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "option2": "\u0918\u091f\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "option3": "\u092c\u0922\u093c\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "option4": "\u0935\u0948\u0938\u0947 \u0939\u0940 \u0930\u0939\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "Answer": "\u0935\u0948\u0938\u0947 \u0939\u0940 \u0930\u0939\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:47:01+00:00", "question": "[15/15] \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0940 \u0935\u093f\u0936\u093f\u0937\u094d\u091f \u0915\u094b\u0921 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u201cFAILURE\u201d \u0915\u094b \u201cFRULIAG\u201d \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948 | \u0907\u0938 \u0915\u094b\u0921 \u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u201cSUCCESS\u201d \u0915\u094b \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u090f\u0917\u093e?", "option1": "TSECCUP", "option2": "SSECCUU", "option3": "TSECCUL", "option4": "TSECUCU", "Answer": "SSECCUU"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:45:59+00:00", "question": "[14/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0936\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0932\u094d\u092a\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0935\u093f\u0937\u092e \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u094b \u091a\u0941\u0928\u093f\u090f|", "option1": "9:729", "option2": "7:343", "option3": "8:512", "option4": "6:226", "Answer": "6:226"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:44:57+00:00", "question": "[13/15] \u0926\u093f\u0935\u094d\u200d\u092f\u093e,\u0935\u093f\u0928\u094b\u0926 \u0915\u0947 \u0909\u0924\u094d\u200d\u0924\u0930-\u092a\u0936\u094d\u200d\u091a\u093f\u092e \u092e\u0947\u0902 10 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940. \u0915\u0940 \u0926\u0942\u0930\u0940 \u092a\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0940\u0924\u093f,\u0926\u093f\u0935\u094d\u200d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u0947 \u0926\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093f\u0923 \u092e\u0947\u0902 6 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940 \u0915\u0940 \u0926\u0942\u0930\u0940 \u092a\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0964\u092a\u094d\u0930\u0940\u0924\u093f, \u0935\u093f\u0928\u094b\u0926 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u0936\u094d\u200d\u091a\u093f\u092e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0939\u0948| \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0940\u0924\u093f \u0914\u0930 \u0935\u093f\u0928\u094b\u0926 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0940\u091a \u0928\u094d\u200d\u092f\u0942\u0928\u0924\u092e \u0926\u0942\u0930\u0940 \u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0947\u0902?", "option1": "7 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940", "option2": "6 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940", "option3": "8 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940", "option4": "10 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940", "Answer": "8 \u0938\u0947\u0902.\u092e\u0940"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:43:55+00:00", "question": "[12/15] \u090f\u0915 \u0928\u093f\u0936\u094d\u200d\u091a\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0942\u091f \u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902, \u2018PUMP\u2019 \u0915\u094b \u2018OTLO\u2019 \u0915\u0947 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0924\u094b \u0909\u0938\u0940 \u0915\u0942\u091f \u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u2018TRUMP\u2019 \u0915\u094b \u0915\u0948\u0938\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u090f\u0917\u093e?", "option1": "MKJOT", "option2": "HTJHY", "option3": "HGERE", "option4": "SQTLO", "Answer": "SQTLO"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:42:54+00:00", "question": "[11/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u200d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0936\u094d\u200d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902, \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0932\u094d\u200d\u092a\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0935\u093f\u0937\u092e \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u200d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u093e \u091a\u092f\u0928 \u0915\u0930\u0947\u0902\u0964", "option1": "37", "option2": "71", "option3": "83", "option4": "77", "Answer": "77"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:41:52+00:00", "question": "[10/15] \u090f\u0915 \u0906\u200d\u0926\u092e\u0940 \u0915\u0940 \u0913\u0930 \u0907\u0936\u093e\u0930\u093e \u0915\u0930\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0941\u090f, \u0938\u093e\u0930\u093e \u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0939\u093e, \u2018\u0935\u0939 \u092e\u0947\u0930\u0947 \u092a\u093f\u0924\u093e \u0915\u0947 \u090f\u0915\u0932\u094c\u0924\u0947 \u0938\u0928-\u0907\u0928-\u0932\u0949 \u0915\u0947 \u0917\u094d\u0930\u0948\u0902\u0921\u0938\u0928 \u0915\u0940 \u092c\u0939\u0928 \u0915\u093e \u092d\u093e\u0908 \u0939\u0948\u2019\u0964 \u0935\u0939 \u0906\u0926\u092e\u0940 \u0938\u093e\u0930\u093e \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0917\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0921\u0921\u0949\u091f\u0930", "option2": "\u0917\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0921\u0938\u0928", "option3": "\u092c\u0947\u091f\u0940", "option4": "\u092c\u0947\u091f\u093e", "Answer": "\u0917\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0921\u0938\u0928"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:40:50+00:00", "question": "[9/15] \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0936\u092c\u094d\u200d\u0926\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0909\u0928\u0915\u0947 \u0936\u092c\u094d\u200d\u0926\u0915\u094b\u0936 \u0905\u0928\u0941\u0915\u094d\u0930\u092e \u0915\u0947 \u0905\u0928\u0941\u0938\u093e\u0930 \u0935\u094d\u200d\u092f\u0935\u0938\u094d\u200d\u0925\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0947\u0902\u0964\n1) Trend\n2) Trump 3) Trust 4) Track 5) Trade", "option1": "45132", "option2": "45213", "option3": "54123", "option4": "45123", "Answer": "45123"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:39:48+00:00", "question": "[8/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0936\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0932\u094d\u092a\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u094b \u091a\u0941\u0928\u093f\u090f|\n\n12 : 60 : : 28 : ?", "option1": "160", "option2": "150", "option3": "145", "option4": "140", "Answer": "140"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:38:46+00:00", "question": "[7/15] \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0940 \u0935\u093f\u0936\u093f\u0937\u094d\u091f \u0915\u094b\u0921 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u201cLIAR\u201d \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948, RANGE\u201d \u0915\u094b \u201c28641\u201d \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948 | \u0907\u0938 \u0915\u094b\u0921 \u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u201cARRANGE\u201d \u0915\u094b \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0932\u093f\u0916\u093e \u091c\u093e\u090f\u0917\u093e?", "option1": "8288641", "option2": "8222641", "option3": "8228641", "option4": "8228614", "Answer": "8228641"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:37:20+00:00", "question": "[6/15] \u0906\u091c \u0938\u094b\u092e\u0935\u093e\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0906\u0916\u093f\u0930\u0940 \u092c\u0941\u0927\u0935\u093e\u0930 \u0915\u094b \u0924\u093e\u0930\u0940\u0916 27 \u0926\u093f\u0938\u092e\u094d\u092c\u0930 1989 \u0925\u0940\u0964 \u0906\u091c \u0915\u0940 \u0926\u093f\u0928\u093e\u0902\u0915 \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "2 \u091c\u0928\u0935\u0930\u0940 1991", "option2": "31 \u0926\u093f\u0938\u092e\u094d\u092c\u0930 1989", "option3": "1 \u091c\u0928\u0935\u0930\u0940 1990", "option4": "30 \u0926\u093f\u0938\u092e\u094d\u092c\u0930 1989", "Answer": "1 \u091c\u0928\u0935\u0930\u0940 1990"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:36:18+00:00", "question": "[5/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u200d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0936\u094d\u200d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902, \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0932\u094d\u200d\u092a\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0935\u093f\u0937\u092e \u0936\u092c\u094d\u200d\u0926 \u0915\u093e \u091a\u092f\u0928 \u0915\u0930\u0947\u0902\u0964", "option1": "\u091c\u0902\u0924\u0941 \u0935\u093f\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928", "option2": "\u0907\u0924\u093f\u0939\u093e\u0938", "option3": "\u0935\u0928\u0938\u094d\u200d\u092a\u0924\u093f \u0935\u093f\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928", "option4": "\u0930\u0938\u093e\u092f\u0928 \u0935\u093f\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928", "Answer": "\u0907\u0924\u093f\u0939\u093e\u0938"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:35:16+00:00", "question": "[4/15] \u0930\u093e\u092e \u0928\u0947 \u090f\u0915 \u0924\u0938\u094d\u200d\u0935\u0940\u0930 \u0915\u0940 \u0913\u0930 \u0907\u0936\u093e\u0930\u093e \u0915\u0930\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0941\u090f \u0915\u0939\u093e \u0915\u093f \u2018\u0935\u0939 \u092e\u0947\u0930\u0940 \u092c\u0939\u0928 \u0915\u0947 \u092d\u093e\u0908 \u0915\u0940 \u092e\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0915\u093e \u092a\u0941\u0924\u094d\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u2019\u0964 \u0924\u0938\u094d\u200d\u0935\u0940\u0930 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u093e \u0935\u094d\u200d\u092f\u0915\u094d\u200d\u0924\u093f \u0930\u093e\u092e \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092a\u093f\u0924\u093e", "option2": "\u0905\u0902\u0915\u0932", "option3": "\u092c\u094d\u0930\u0926\u0930-\u0907\u0928-\u0932\u0949", "option4": "\u092d\u093e\u0908", "Answer": "\u092d\u093e\u0908"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:34:14+00:00", "question": "[3/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u0936\u092c\u094d\u0926\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0936\u092c\u094d\u0926\u0915\u094b\u0936 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0906\u0928\u0947 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u0947 \u0915\u094d\u0930\u092e \u0915\u0947 \u0905\u0928\u0941\u0938\u093e\u0930 \u0932\u093f\u0916\u0947\u0902|\n\n1) Journey 2) Judge 3) Jingling 4) Jingle 5) Judgement", "option1": "32541", "option2": "53142", "option3": "43125", "option4": "15342", "Answer": "43125"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:33:13+00:00", "question": "[2/15] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0936\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0932\u094d\u092a\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u094b \u091a\u0941\u0928\u093f\u090f|\n11 :6 : :15 : ?", "option1": "19", "option2": "8", "option3": "11", "option4": "7", "Answer": "8"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 11:32:11+00:00", "question": "[1/15] 20 \u0932\u0921\u093c\u0915\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0940 \u090f\u0915 \u092a\u0902\u0915\u094d\u200d\u0924\u093f \u092e\u0947\u0902, A \u0915\u093e \u0938\u094d\u200d\u0925\u093e\u0928 \u0926\u093e\u090f\u0902 \u091b\u094b\u0930 \u0938\u0947 \u0938\u093e\u0924\u0935\u093e\u0902 \u0914\u0930 B \u0915\u093e \u0938\u094d\u200d\u0925\u093e\u0928 \u092c\u093e\u090f\u0902 \u091b\u094b\u0930 \u0938\u0947 10\u0935\u093e\u0902 \u0939\u0948\u0964 A \u0914\u0930 B \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0940\u091a \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u0932\u0921\u093c\u0915\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "9", "option2": "5", "option3": "3", "option4": "7", "Answer": "3"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:40:06+00:00", "question": "[10/10] (1/16)^-5/4 \u092c\u0930\u093e\u092c\u0930 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "32", "option2": "42", "option3": "22", "option4": "25", "Answer": "32"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:39:04+00:00", "question": "[9/10] \u0926\u094b \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e\u090f\u0902 36 \u0924\u0925\u093e 54 \u0915\u093e \u092e\u0939\u0924\u094d\u0924\u092e \u0938\u092e\u093e\u092a\u0935\u0930\u094d\u0924\u0915(HCF) 9 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0909\u0928\u0915\u0947 \u0932\u0918\u0941\u0924\u094d\u0924\u092e \u0938\u092e\u093e\u092a\u0935\u0930\u094d\u0924\u0915(LCM) \u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0924 \u0915\u0940\u091c\u093f\u090f\u00ae", "option1": "220", "option2": "214", "option3": "218", "option4": "216", "Answer": "216"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:38:02+00:00", "question": "[8/10] \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0940 \u0935\u0943\u0924\u094d\u0924 \u0915\u0940 \u0924\u094d\u0930\u093f\u091c\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u094b 12% \u0938\u0947 \u092c\u0922\u093c\u093e \u0926\u0947\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u0947 \u0909\u0938\u0915\u0947 \u0915\u094d\u0937\u0947\u0924\u094d\u0930\u092b\u0932 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u093f\u0936\u0924 \u0915\u0940 \u0935\u0943\u0926\u094d\u0927\u093f \u0939\u094b\u0917\u0940?", "option1": "24%", "option2": "25%", "option3": "25.44 %", "option4": "24.44%", "Answer": "25.44 %"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:37:00+00:00", "question": "[7/10] \u092f\u0926\u093f 6 \u0915\u094d\u0930\u092e\u093f\u0915 \u0938\u092e \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0913\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u0914\u0938\u0924 25 \u0939\u094b, \u0924\u094b \u0909\u0928\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u092c\u0938\u0947 \u092c\u0921\u093c\u0940 \u0914\u0930 \u0938\u092c\u0938\u0947 \u091b\u094b\u091f\u0940 \u0938\u0902\u0916\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u093e \u0905\u0902\u0924\u0930 \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u093e \u0939\u094b\u0917\u093e?", "option1": "12", "option2": "8", "option3": "14", "option4": "10", "Answer": "10"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:35:58+00:00", "question": "[6/10] \u091c\u092c \u20b94 \u092e\u0947\u0902 5 \u0928\u0940\u0902\u092c\u0942 \u0916\u0930\u0940\u0926 \u0915\u0930 \u20b95 \u092e\u0947\u0902 4 \u0928\u093f\u0902\u092c\u0942 \u092c\u0947\u091a\u0947 \u091c\u093e\u090f\u0902 \u0924\u094b \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u093f\u0936\u0924 \u0932\u093e\u092d \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0939\u094b\u0917\u093e\u00ae", "option1": "56%", "option2": "57 1/4%", "option3": "57 %", "option4": "56 1/4%", "Answer": "56 1/4%"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:34:57+00:00", "question": "[5/10] ( 264)\u00b9\u2070\u00b2 \u0915\u093e \u0907\u0915\u093e\u0908 \u0905\u0902\u0915 \u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0924 \u0915\u0940\u091c\u093f\u090f", "option1": "2", "option2": "6", "option3": "4", "option4": "0", "Answer": "6"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:33:55+00:00", "question": "[4/10] \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0940 \u0938\u092e\u091a\u0924\u0941\u0930\u094d\u092d\u0941\u091c(Rhombus) \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u094d\u092f\u0947\u0915 \u092d\u0941\u091c\u093e \u0915\u0940 \u0932\u0902\u092c\u093e\u0908 25 \u092e\u0940\u091f\u0930 \u0914\u0930 \u090f\u0915 \u0935\u093f\u0915\u0930\u094d\u0923 \u0915\u0940 \u0932\u0902\u092c\u093e\u0908 14 \u092e\u0940\u091f\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0938\u092e\u091a\u0924\u0941\u0930\u094d\u092d\u0941\u091c \u0915\u093e \u0915\u094d\u0937\u0947\u0924\u094d\u0930\u092b\u0932 \u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u093f\u090f?", "option1": "175 m\u00b2", "option2": "336 m\u00b2", "option3": "350 m\u00b2", "option4": "168 m\u00b2", "Answer": "336 m\u00b2"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:32:53+00:00", "question": "[3/10] \u092f\u0926\u093f x \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0940 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092f \u0915\u094b 4 \u0918\u0902\u091f\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u092e\u093e\u092a\u094d\u0924 \u0915\u0930 \u0938\u0915\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948 \u0914\u0930 y \u0938\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092f \u0915\u094b 8 \u0918\u0902\u091f\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u094d\u0935\u0924\u0902\u0924\u094d\u0930 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u0938\u0947 \u0938\u092e\u093e\u092a\u094d\u0924 \u0915\u0930 \u0938\u0915\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948, \u0924\u094b \u0935\u0947 \u090f\u0915 \u0938\u093e\u0925 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092f \u0938\u092e\u093e\u092a\u094d\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0947\u0902\u0917\u0947", "option1": "160 \u092e\u093f\u0928\u091f", "option2": "140 \u092e\u093f\u0928\u091f", "option3": "120 \u092e\u093f\u0928\u091f", "option4": "150 \u092e\u093f\u0928\u091f", "Answer": "160 \u092e\u093f\u0928\u091f"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:31:51+00:00", "question": "[2/10] \u092f\u0926\u093f 3^x+8 = 27^ 2x+1\n\u0924\u092c x \u0915\u093e \u092e\u093e\u0928 \u0939\u0948", "option1": "1", "option2": "3", "option3": "-3", "option4": "7", "Answer": "1"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 10:30:49+00:00", "question": "[1/10] \u20b9900 \u0915\u094b A,B,C \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092c\u093e\u0902\u091f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u090f \u0914\u0930 \u0909\u0938\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092c\u0902\u091f\u0935\u093e\u0930\u093e \u0907\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0939\u094b \u0915\u093f A \u0930\u093e\u0936\u093f \u0915\u093e 1/2 =B \u0915\u0940 \u0930\u093e\u0936\u093f \u0915\u093e 1/3 = C \u0915\u0940 \u0930\u093e\u0936\u093f \u0915\u093e 1/4, \u0924\u094b A,B,C \u0926\u094d\u0935\u093e\u0930\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u093e\u092a\u094d\u0924 \u0915\u0940 \u0917\u0908 \u0930\u093e\u0936\u093f (\u0930\u0941 \u092e\u0947\u0902) \u0915\u093f\u0924\u0928\u0940 \u0939\u094b\u0917\u0940?", "option1": "200, 300, 400", "option2": "350, 450, 100", "option3": "400, 150, 350", "option4": "300, 400, 200", "Answer": "200, 300, 400"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 09:02:05+00:00", "question": "[30/30] \u0905\u0927\u094d\u092f\u093e\u092a\u0928 \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u0923 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e \u0915\u0940 \u0935\u093f\u0927\u093f \u0915\u093e \u091a\u092f\u0928 \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0915\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0915 \u092a\u0930 \u0928\u093f\u0930\u094d\u092d\u0930 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0915\u0930\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0938\u0902\u0938\u093e\u0927\u0928\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0940 \u0909\u092a\u0932\u092c\u094d\u0927\u0924\u093e", "option2": "\u0935\u093f\u0926\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0932\u092f \u0915\u093e \u0926\u0930\u094d\u0936\u0928\u0936\u093e\u0938\u094d\u0924\u094d\u0930", "option3": "\u0926\u094b\u0928\u094b\u0902", "option4": "\u0907\u0928\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902", "Answer": "\u0935\u093f\u0926\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0932\u092f \u0915\u093e \u0926\u0930\u094d\u0936\u0928\u0936\u093e\u0938\u094d\u0924\u094d\u0930"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 09:01:33+00:00", "question": "[29/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0938\u0902\u0936\u094d\u0932\u0947\u0937\u0923 \u0915\u0940 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092e\u0939\u0924\u094d\u0935\u092a\u0942\u0930\u094d\u0923 \u092d\u0942\u092e\u093f\u0915\u093e \u0928\u093f\u092d\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092a\u0930\u094d\u0923\u0939\u0930\u093f\u0924", "option2": "\u0938\u0948\u0902\u091f\u0930\u094b\u0938\u094b\u092e", "option3": "\u091f\u094b\u0928\u094b\u092a\u094d\u0932\u093e\u0938\u094d\u091f", "option4": "\u0928\u0947\u092e\u0947\u0902\u091f\u094b\u092a\u094d\u0932\u093e\u0938\u094d\u091f", "Answer": "\u092a\u0930\u094d\u0923\u0939\u0930\u093f\u0924"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 09:01:01+00:00", "question": "[28/30] \u0928\u0940\u091a\u0947 \u0926\u093f\u092f\u093e \u0917\u092f\u093e \u092a\u0948\u0930\u093e\u0917\u094d\u0930\u093e\u092b \u092a\u0922\u093c\u093f\u090f-\n\"\u092e\u0948\u0902 \u0917\u093e\u0902\u0901\u0935 \u0938\u0947 \u0906\u092f\u093e \u0939\u0942\u0902\u0901\u0964 \u0939\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0947 \u0917\u093e\u0902\u0901\u0935 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0905\u0924\u094d\u092f\u0927\u093f\u0915 \u0935\u0930\u094d\u0937\u093e \u0939\u094b\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0907\u0938\u0932\u093f\u090f \u0939\u092e\u093e\u0930\u0947 \u0918\u0930 \u0927\u0930\u0924\u0940 \u0938\u0947 \u0932\u0917\u092d\u0917 10 \u0938\u0947 12 \u092b\u0941\u091f (3 \u0938\u0947 3.5) \u090a\u0902\u0901\u091a\u0947 \u092c\u0928\u0947 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902\u0964 \u0907\u0928\u094d\u0939\u0947\u0902 \u092e\u091c\u092c\u0942\u0924 \u092c\u093e\u0902\u0901\u0938 \u0915\u0947 \u0916\u0902\u092d\u094b\u0902 \u092a\u0930 \u092c\u0928\u093e\u092f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u092f\u0939 \u0918\u0930 \u0905\u0902\u0926\u0930 \u0938\u0947 \u092d\u0940 \u0932\u0915\u0921\u093c\u0940 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0928\u0947 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "\u0924\u092e\u093f\u0932\u0928\u093e\u0921\u0941 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option2": "\u0909\u0924\u094d\u0924\u0930\u093e\u0916\u0902\u0921 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option3": "\u0906\u0902\u0927\u094d\u0930 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0926\u0947\u0936 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option4": "\u0905\u0938\u092e \u092e\u0947\u0902", "Answer": "\u0905\u0938\u092e \u092e\u0947\u0902"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 09:00:29+00:00", "question": "[27/30] \u0913\u0923\u092e, \u092b\u0938\u0932 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u090f\u0915 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0938\u093f\u0926\u094d\u0927 \u0924\u094d\u092f\u094c\u0939\u093e\u0930 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u092f\u0939 \u0924\u094d\u092f\u094b\u0939\u093e\u0930 \u092d\u093e\u0930\u0924 \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0930\u093e\u091c\u094d\u092f \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092e\u0928\u093e\u092f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0915\u0947\u0930\u0932", "option2": "\u0924\u092e\u093f\u0932\u0928\u093e\u0921\u0941", "option3": "\u0924\u0947\u0932\u0902\u0917\u093e\u0928\u093e", "option4": "\u0938\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0915\u093f\u092e", "Answer": "\u0915\u0947\u0930\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:59:58+00:00", "question": "[26/30] \u0930\u093e\u0928\u0940 \u0926\u0941\u0930\u094d\u0917\u093e\u0935\u0924\u0940 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u091c\u0928\u091c\u093e\u0924\u093f \u0930\u093e\u091c\u094d\u092f \u0938\u0947 \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927\u093f\u0924 \u0925\u0940?", "option1": "\u092d\u0940\u0932", "option2": "\u0917\u094b\u0902\u0921", "option3": "\u092e\u0941\u0902\u0921\u093e", "option4": "\u0938\u0902\u0925\u093e\u0932", "Answer": "\u0917\u094b\u0902\u0921"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:59:26+00:00", "question": "[25/30] \u0932\u0926\u094d\u0926\u093e\u0916 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u094b\u0917 \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u0918\u0930\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0940 \u0928\u093f\u091a\u0932\u0940 \u092e\u0902\u091c\u093f\u0932 \u0915\u093e \u0909\u092a\u092f\u094b\u0917 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0915\u0930\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "\u0916\u093e\u0928\u093e \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f", "option2": "\u092e\u0947\u0939\u092e\u093e\u0928\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0920\u0939\u0930\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f", "option3": "\u0938\u093e\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u0914\u0930 \u091c\u0940\u0935\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0930\u0916\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f", "option4": "\u0938\u092d\u0940 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f", "Answer": "\u0938\u093e\u092e\u093e\u0928 \u0914\u0930 \u091c\u0940\u0935\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0930\u0916\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:58:54+00:00", "question": "[24/30] \u091a\u093e\u0902\u0917\u092a\u093e \u091c\u0928\u091c\u093e\u0924\u093f \u0915\u0947 \u0926\u094d\u0935\u093e\u0930\u093e \u092c\u0928\u093e\u092f\u0947 \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u0947 \u0905\u0938\u094d\u0925\u093e\u0908 \u0928\u093f\u0935\u093e\u0938 (\u0906\u0936\u094d\u0930\u092f) \u0915\u094b \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u0939\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0930\u0947\u092c\u094b", "option2": "\u0930\u0947\u0928\u092c\u094b", "option3": "\u092e\u094b\u0917\u0948\u092e\u094d\u092c\u094b", "option4": "\u0938\u094b\u0917\u0948\u092e\u094d\u092c\u094b", "Answer": "\u0930\u0947\u092c\u094b"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:58:22+00:00", "question": "[23/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u090f\u0915 \u0917\u0948\u0930-\u0914\u092a\u091a\u093e\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093e \u0915\u093e \u0909\u0926\u093e\u0939\u0930\u0923 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092c\u091a\u094d\u091a\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u092a\u0924\u094d\u0930\u093e\u091a\u093e\u0930 \u0915\u0947 \u092e\u093e\u0927\u094d\u092f\u092e \u0938\u0947 \u092a\u093e\u0920 \u0938\u0940\u0916\u0928\u093e", "option2": "\u092c\u091a\u094d\u091a\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u092e\u093e\u0924\u093e-\u092a\u093f\u0924\u093e \u0938\u0947 \u0916\u093e\u0928\u093e \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0928\u093e \u0938\u0940\u0916\u0928\u093e", "option3": "\u092f\u0939 \u0938\u0902\u0930\u091a\u093f\u0924 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948", "option4": "\u0917\u0948\u0930 \u0914\u092a\u091a\u093e\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0928\u092c\u0942\u091d\u0915\u0930 \u0915\u0940 \u091c\u093e \u0938\u0915\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948 \u0932\u0947\u0915\u093f\u0928 \u091c\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0926\u093e\u0924\u0930 \u092e\u093e\u092e\u0932\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0910\u0938\u093e \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948", "Answer": "\u092c\u091a\u094d\u091a\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u092e\u093e\u0924\u093e-\u092a\u093f\u0924\u093e \u0938\u0947 \u0916\u093e\u0928\u093e \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0928\u093e \u0938\u0940\u0916\u0928\u093e"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:57:50+00:00", "question": "[22/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u092a\u0915\u094d\u0937\u0940 \u0915\u093e \u0918\u094b\u0902\u0938\u0932\u093e \u0932\u093e\u0932\u091f\u0947\u0928 \u0915\u0940 \u0924\u0930\u0939 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0915\u0920\u092b\u094b\u0921\u093c\u0935\u093e", "option2": "\u0926\u0930\u094d\u091c\u093f\u0928", "option3": "\u0915\u092c\u0942\u0924\u0930", "option4": "\u0935\u0940\u0935\u0930", "Answer": "\u0935\u0940\u0935\u0930"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:57:19+00:00", "question": "[21/30] \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0938\u0902\u0936\u094d\u0932\u0947\u0937\u0923 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u092c\u0938\u0947 \u0915\u092e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0935\u0940 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0928\u0940\u0932\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936", "option2": "\u0939\u0930\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936", "option3": "\u0932\u093e\u0932 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936", "option4": "\u0938\u0942\u0930\u094d\u092f \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936", "Answer": "\u0939\u0930\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:56:47+00:00", "question": "[20/30] \u0916\u0924\u092e\u092c\u0902\u0926 \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u091f\u0947\u0902\u091f\u094b \u0915\u093e \u0909\u0916\u093e\u0921\u093c\u0928\u093e", "option2": "\u0932\u0915\u0921\u093c\u0940 \u0915\u0940 \u0928\u0915\u094d\u0915\u093e\u0936\u0940", "option3": "\u092a\u0924\u094d\u0925\u0930 \u0915\u0940 \u0928\u0915\u094d\u0915\u093e\u0936\u0940", "option4": "\u0907\u0928\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902", "Answer": "\u0932\u0915\u0921\u093c\u0940 \u0915\u0940 \u0928\u0915\u094d\u0915\u093e\u0936\u0940"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:56:15+00:00", "question": "[19/30] \u092e\u0938\u093e\u0932\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u0918\u0930 \u0915\u093f\u0938\u0947 \u0915\u0939\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "\u0917\u094b\u0935\u093e", "option2": "\u0915\u0930\u094d\u0928\u093e\u091f\u0915", "option3": "\u0906\u0902\u0927\u094d\u0930 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0926\u0947\u0936", "option4": "\u0915\u0947\u0930\u0932", "Answer": "\u0915\u0947\u0930\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:55:43+00:00", "question": "[18/30] \u0905\u092e\u0930\u092c\u0947\u0932 \u0909\u0926\u093e\u0939\u0930\u0923 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0930\u0947\u0936\u0947\u0926\u093e\u0930 \u091c\u0921\u093c \u0915\u093e", "option2": "\u092a\u0930\u091c\u0940\u0935\u0940 \u091c\u0921\u093c \u0915\u093e", "option3": "\u0905\u0935\u0938\u094d\u0924\u0902\u092d \u091c\u0921\u093c \u0915\u093e", "option4": "\u0938\u094d\u0924\u0902\u092d \u091c\u0921\u093c \u0915\u093e", "Answer": "\u092a\u0930\u091c\u0940\u0935\u0940 \u091c\u0921\u093c \u0915\u093e"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:55:12+00:00", "question": "[17/30] \u0915\u0930\u094d\u091f\u0932\u0947\u0935\u093f\u0928 \u0928\u0947 _______ \u0915\u094b \u0938\u092e\u091d\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0936\u092c\u094d\u0926 '\u091c\u0940\u0935\u0928 \u0905\u0902\u0924\u0930\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937' \u0915\u093e \u0907\u0938\u094d\u0924\u0947\u092e\u093e\u0932 \u0915\u093f\u092f\u093e \u0917\u092f\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092d\u094c\u0924\u093f\u0915 \u0935\u093e\u0924\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923", "option2": "\u092e\u0928\u094b\u0935\u0948\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928\u093f\u0915 \u092e\u093e\u0939\u094c\u0932", "option3": "\u091c\u0948\u0935\u093f\u0915 \u092a\u0930\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923", "option4": "\u0938\u093e\u0902\u0938\u094d\u0915\u0943\u0924\u093f\u0915 \u0935\u093e\u0924\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923", "Answer": "\u092e\u0928\u094b\u0935\u0948\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928\u093f\u0915 \u092e\u093e\u0939\u094c\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:54:40+00:00", "question": "[16/30] '\u0915\u0941\u0921\u0941\u0915' \u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u091c\u0902\u0917\u0932 \u0915\u094b \u0915\u0939\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "\u0924\u094b\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0917", "option2": "\u0914\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0917", "option3": "\u0935\u093f\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0917", "option4": "\u0907\u0928\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902", "Answer": "\u0924\u094b\u0930\u093e\u0902\u0917"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:54:08+00:00", "question": "[15/30] \u0915\u0936\u094d\u092e\u0940\u0930 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u093e\u0908 \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u0940 \u0928\u0915\u094d\u0915\u093e\u0936\u0940 \u0930\u0939\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u093e\u0909\u0938\u092c\u094b\u091f \u0915\u0939\u0932\u093e\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0936\u093f\u0915\u093e\u0930\u093e", "option2": "\u0921\u094b\u0902\u0917\u093e", "option3": "\u0930\u0947\u092c\u094b", "option4": "\u0907\u0917\u094d\u0932\u0942", "Answer": "\u0921\u094b\u0902\u0917\u093e"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:53:36+00:00", "question": "[14/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092c\u092f\u093e\u0928\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928-\u0938\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0925\u092e\u093f\u0915 \u0938\u094d\u0924\u0930 \u092a\u0930 \u0908.\u0935\u0940.\u090f\u0938. \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u0923 \u0915\u093e \u090f\u0915 \u0909\u0926\u094d\u0926\u0947\u0936\u094d\u092f \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092a\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0915\u0943\u0924\u093f\u0915 \u0914\u0930 \u0938\u093e\u092e\u093e\u091c\u093f\u0915 \u0935\u093e\u0924\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u093e\u0930\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0909\u0924\u094d\u0938\u0941\u0915\u0924\u093e \u091c\u0917\u093e\u0928\u093e", "option2": "\u0905\u0928\u094d\u0935\u0947\u0937\u0923 \u0914\u0930 \u0917\u0924\u093f\u0935\u093f\u0927\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u092a\u0930 \u0935\u094d\u092f\u0938\u094d\u0924 \u0930\u0916\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0941\u090f \u0938\u0902\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0928\u093e\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0915 \u0914\u0930 \u092e\u0928\u094b\u092a\u094d\u0930\u0947\u0930\u0923\u093e \u0915\u094c\u0936\u0932 \u0915\u093e \u0935\u093f\u0915\u093e\u0938 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u093e", "option3": "\u092e\u0942\u0932\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0902\u0915\u0928 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093e\u0930\u094d\u0925\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0928\u093f\u092f\u092e \u0914\u0930 \u092a\u0930\u093f\u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092c\u0924\u093e\u0928\u093e", "option4": "\u091c\u0940\u0935\u0928 \u0914\u0930 \u092a\u0930\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u091a\u093f\u0902\u0924\u093e \u0915\u0947 \u0935\u093f\u0937\u092f \u0915\u0947 \u092e\u0942\u0932\u094d\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0906\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0938\u093e\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f", "Answer": "\u092e\u0942\u0932\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0902\u0915\u0928 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0936\u093f\u0915\u094d\u0937\u093e\u0930\u094d\u0925\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u094b \u0928\u093f\u092f\u092e \u0914\u0930 \u092a\u0930\u093f\u092d\u093e\u0937\u093e \u092c\u0924\u093e\u0928\u093e"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:53:04+00:00", "question": "[13/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928-\u0938\u093e \u0909\u0926\u093e\u0939\u0930\u0923 \u0909\u0926\u094d\u0926\u0940\u092a\u0928- \u0905\u0928\u0941\u0915\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u094d\u0930\u093f\u092f\u093e \u0915\u094b \u0926\u0930\u094d\u0936\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0915\u0949\u0915\u0930\u094b\u091a \u0915\u093e \u0930\u094b\u0936\u0928\u0940 \u0926\u0947\u0916\u0915\u0930 \u091b\u093f\u092a \u091c\u093e\u0928\u093e", "option2": "\u0938\u0942\u0930\u091c \u091b\u093f\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u0936\u094d\u091a\u093e\u0924\u094d \u092b\u0942\u0932\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u093e \u092c\u0902\u0926 \u0939\u094b\u0928\u093e", "option3": "\u092e\u0928-\u092a\u0938\u0902\u0926 \u0935\u094d\u092f\u0902\u091c\u0928 \u0926\u0947\u0916 \u0915\u0930 \u092e\u0941\u0902\u0901\u0939 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u093e\u0928\u0940 \u0906\u0928\u093e", "option4": "\u0909\u092a\u0930\u094b\u0915\u094d\u0924 \u0938\u092d\u0940", "Answer": "\u0909\u092a\u0930\u094b\u0915\u094d\u0924 \u0938\u092d\u0940"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:52:33+00:00", "question": "[12/30] \u092a\u0930\u093f\u0927\u093f \u0939\u092e\u0947\u0936\u093e \u092e\u093f\u091f\u094d\u091f\u0940 \u0938\u0947 \u091a\u0940\u091c\u0947\u0902 \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948 \u0914\u0930 \u0909\u0928\u094d\u0939\u0947\u0902 \u092c\u093f\u0917\u093e\u0921\u093c\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948 \u0914\u0930 \u092b\u093f\u0930 \u0938\u0947 \u091a\u0940\u091c\u0947\u0902 \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948\u0964 \u0907\u0938 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0930 \u0915\u0947 \u0916\u0947\u0932 \u0938\u0947 \u0909\u0938\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0915\u093f\u0938 \u091a\u0940\u091c \u0915\u093e \u0935\u093f\u0915\u093e\u0938 \u0939\u094b\u0917\u093e?", "option1": "\u091c\u093f\u091c\u094d\u091e\u093e\u0938\u093e \u0915\u093e", "option2": "\u0936\u0930\u0940\u0930 \u0915\u093e", "option3": "\u0930\u091a\u0928\u093e\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0915 \u0917\u0941\u0923", "option4": "\u0930\u094b\u092e\u093e\u0902\u091a\u0915\u093e\u0930\u0940 \u0916\u0947\u0932", "Answer": "\u0930\u091a\u0928\u093e\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0915 \u0917\u0941\u0923"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:52:01+00:00", "question": "[11/30] \u092d\u093e\u0930\u0924 \u0915\u0940 \u091c\u0928\u091c\u093e\u0924\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u092c\u0938\u0947 \u092c\u0921\u093c\u0940 \u091c\u0928\u091c\u093e\u0924\u093f \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092e\u0941\u0902\u0921\u093e", "option2": "\u0938\u0902\u0925\u093e\u0932", "option3": "\u0917\u0926\u094d\u0926\u0940", "option4": "\u0917\u094b\u0902\u0921", "Answer": "\u0917\u094b\u0902\u0921"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:51:29+00:00", "question": "[10/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u0938\u092e\u0942\u0939 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0909\u0938 \u0938\u092e\u0942\u0939 \u0915\u094b \u091a\u0941\u0928\u093f\u090f \u091c\u093f\u0938\u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0916\u093e\u0928\u093e \u092a\u0915\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0924\u0930\u0940\u0915\u0947 (\u0922\u0902\u0917) \u0926\u093f\u090f \u0917\u090f \u0939\u0948\u0902?", "option1": "\u0924\u0932\u0915\u0930, \u092d\u093f\u0917\u094b\u0915\u0930, \u092d\u0942\u0928\u0915\u0930", "option2": "\u0938\u0947\u0902\u0915\u0915\u0930, \u0924\u0932\u0915\u0930, \u092d\u0942\u0928\u0915\u0930", "option3": "\u0909\u092c\u093e\u0932\u0915\u0930, \u0917\u0942\u0901\u0927\u0915\u0930, \u092d\u0942\u0928\u0915\u0930", "option4": "\u0938\u0947\u0902\u0915\u0915\u0930, \u0909\u092c\u093e\u0932\u0915\u0930, \u092c\u0947\u0932\u0915\u0930", "Answer": "\u0938\u0947\u0902\u0915\u0915\u0930, \u0924\u0932\u0915\u0930, \u092d\u0942\u0928\u0915\u0930"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:50:57+00:00", "question": "[9/30] \u0928\u093e\u0917\u092b\u0928\u0940 (\u0915\u0948\u0915\u094d\u091f\u0938) \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0938\u0902\u0936\u094d\u0932\u0947\u0937\u0923 \u0939\u094b\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option2": "\u092a\u0924\u094d\u0924\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option3": "\u0926\u094b\u0928\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902", "option4": "\u0915\u093e\u0902\u0901\u091f\u094b \u092e\u0947\u0902", "Answer": "\u0924\u0928\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:50:25+00:00", "question": "[8/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u0915\u0925\u0928\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928-\u0938\u093e \u0915\u0925\u0928 \u0905\u0938\u0924\u094d\u092f \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u0915\u0947\u0902\u091a\u0941\u0906 \u092a\u093e\u0932\u0928 \u0935\u0930\u094d\u092e\u0940\u0915\u0932\u094d\u091a\u0930 \u0915\u0939\u0932\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948", "option2": "\u0930\u0947\u0936\u092e \u0915\u0947 \u0915\u0940\u0921\u093c\u0947 \u0936\u0939\u0924\u0942\u0924 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u0947\u0921\u093c\u094b\u0902 \u092a\u0930 \u092a\u093e\u0932\u0947 \u091c\u093e\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902", "option3": "\u0915\u0943\u0937\u093f \u0915\u094b \u0938\u092c\u0938\u0947 \u091c\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0926\u093e \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092d\u093e\u0935\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u0947 \u0935\u093e\u0932\u093e \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0915 \u0939\u0948-\u091c\u0932\u0935\u093e\u092f\u0941", "option4": "\u0909\u092a\u0930\u094b\u0915\u094d\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902", "Answer": "\u0909\u092a\u0930\u094b\u0915\u094d\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094b\u0908 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:49:54+00:00", "question": "[7/30] \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0915\u093e\u0936 \u0938\u0902\u0936\u094d\u0932\u0947\u0937\u0923\u093e\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0915  \u0935\u0930\u094d\u0923\u0915 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092a\u0930\u094d\u0923\u0939\u0930\u093f\u0924", "option2": "\u095e\u093e\u092f\u0915\u094b\u092c\u093f\u0932\u093f\u0928", "option3": "\u0915\u0948\u0930\u094b\u091f\u093f\u0928\u0949\u0907\u0921", "option4": "\u090f\u0902\u0925\u094b\u0938\u093e\u092f\u0928\u093f\u0928", "Answer": "\u090f\u0902\u0925\u094b\u0938\u093e\u092f\u0928\u093f\u0928"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:49:22+00:00", "question": "[6/30] \u0938\u093f\u0930\u0915\u0947 \u0915\u093e \u0930\u093e\u0938\u093e\u092f\u0928\u093f\u0915 \u0928\u093e\u092e \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u090f\u0938\u0940\u091f\u094b\u0928", "option2": "\u090f\u0938\u093f\u091f\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option3": "\u092b\u0949\u0930\u092e\u0947\u090f\u0932\u094d\u0921\u093f\u0939\u093e\u0907\u0921", "option4": "\u090f\u0925\u0947\u0928\u0949\u0932", "Answer": "\u090f\u0938\u093f\u091f\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:48:50+00:00", "question": "[5/30] \u0932\u0917\u092d\u0917 \u0938\u092d\u0940 \u092a\u0915\u094d\u0937\u0940 \u0905\u0902\u0921\u0947 \u0926\u0947\u0928\u0947 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0918\u094b\u0902\u0938\u0932\u0947 \u092c\u0928\u093e\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902\u0964 \u0905\u0902\u0921\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u092c\u091a\u094d\u091a\u0947 \u0928\u093f\u0915\u0932 \u0906\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902 \u0924\u092c \u0935\u0947 \u0918\u094b\u0902\u0938\u0932\u093e \u091b\u094b\u0921\u093c \u0926\u0947\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902\u0964 \u092a\u0930\u0902\u0924\u0941 \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928-\u0938\u093e \u092a\u0915\u094d\u0937\u0940 \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u0918\u094b\u0902\u0938\u0932\u0947 \u0915\u094b \u0938\u093e\u0932-\u0926\u0930-\u0938\u093e\u0932 \u0909\u092a\u092f\u094b\u0917 \u0915\u0930\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u091a\u0940\u0932", "option2": "\u0915\u092c\u0942\u0924\u0930", "option3": "\u092e\u094b\u0930", "option4": "\u0938\u092d\u0940", "Answer": "\u091a\u0940\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:48:02+00:00", "question": "[4/30] \u0908.\u0935\u0940.\u090f\u0938. \u0915\u0947 \u090f\u0915\u0940\u0915\u0943\u0924 \u0926\u0943\u0937\u094d\u091f\u093f\u0915\u094b\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u093e\u0930\u0947 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928\u0932\u093f\u0916\u093f\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928-\u0938\u093e \u0938\u0939\u0940 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092a\u094d\u0930\u093e\u0915\u0943\u0924\u093f\u0915, \u0938\u093e\u092e\u093e\u091c\u093f\u0915 \u0914\u0930 \u0938\u093e\u0902\u0938\u094d\u0915\u0943\u0924\u093f\u0915 \u092a\u0930\u094d\u092f\u093e\u0935\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0940\u091a \u0938\u0902\u092c\u0902\u0927 \u0938\u094d\u0925\u093e\u092a\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u093e", "option2": "\u092f\u0939 \u0925\u0940\u092e \u0906\u0927\u093e\u0930\u093f\u0924 \u0939\u0948", "option3": "\u0905\u0927\u093f\u0915\u0924\u092e \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0915\u093e\u0930\u0940 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u093f\u0927\u093e\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u094b \u092a\u094d\u0930\u094b\u0924\u094d\u0938\u093e\u0939\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u093e", "option4": "\u092f\u0939 \u0935\u093f\u091a\u093e\u0930\u094b\u0924\u094d\u0924\u0947\u091c\u0915 \u0939\u0948 \u0914\u0930 \u0928\u093f\u0926\u0947\u0936\u093e\u0924\u094d\u092e\u0915 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0939\u0948", "Answer": "\u0905\u0927\u093f\u0915\u0924\u092e \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0915\u093e\u0930\u0940 \u0915\u0947 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u0924\u093f\u0927\u093e\u0930\u0923 \u0915\u094b \u092a\u094d\u0930\u094b\u0924\u094d\u0938\u093e\u0939\u093f\u0924 \u0915\u0930\u0928\u093e"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:47:19+00:00", "question": "[3/30] \u0910\u0938\u094d\u0915\u093f\u092e\u094b \u0905\u092a\u0928\u0947 \u0918\u0930 '\u0907\u0917\u094d\u0932\u0942' \u0915\u093e \u0928\u093f\u0930\u094d\u092e\u093e\u0923 \u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u0930\u0924\u0947 \u0939\u0948\u0902\u0964 \u0907\u0938\u0915\u093e \u0915\u094d\u092f\u093e \u0915\u093e\u0930\u0923 \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u0920\u0902\u0921\u0940 \u0939\u0935\u093e \u0914\u0930 \u092a\u093e\u0928\u0940 \u0915\u094b \u0905\u0902\u0926\u0930 \u0928\u0939\u0940\u0902 \u0906\u0928\u0947 \u0926\u0947\u0924\u093e", "option2": "\u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u0915\u0940 \u0926\u0940\u0935\u093e\u0930\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0940\u091a \u092e\u094c\u091c\u0942\u0926 \u0939\u0935\u093e \u0905\u0902\u0926\u0930 \u0915\u0940 \u0917\u0930\u094d\u092e\u0940 \u0915\u094b \u092c\u093e\u0939\u0930 \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u0947 \u0930\u094b\u0915\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948", "option3": "\u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u092e\u0941\u092b\u094d\u0924 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092e\u093f\u0932\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948, \u0905\u0928\u094d\u092f \u0938\u093e\u092e\u0917\u094d\u0930\u0940 \u0915\u0940 \u0915\u0940\u092e\u0924 \u0905\u0927\u093f\u0915 \u0939\u094b\u0917\u0940", "option4": "\u0927\u094d\u0930\u0941\u0935\u0940\u092f \u0915\u094d\u0937\u0947\u0924\u094d\u0930\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0915\u0947\u0935\u0932 \u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u0939\u0940 \u0909\u092a\u0932\u092c\u094d\u0927 \u0939\u0948", "Answer": "\u092c\u0930\u094d\u092b \u0915\u0940 \u0926\u0940\u0935\u093e\u0930\u094b\u0902 \u0915\u0947 \u092c\u0940\u091a \u092e\u094c\u091c\u0942\u0926 \u0939\u0935\u093e \u0905\u0902\u0926\u0930 \u0915\u0940 \u0917\u0930\u094d\u092e\u0940 \u0915\u094b \u092c\u093e\u0939\u0930 \u091c\u093e\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u0947 \u0930\u094b\u0915\u0924\u0940 \u0939\u0948"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:46:47+00:00", "question": "[2/30] \u0917\u0930\u094d\u092e\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0905\u0924\u094d\u092f\u0927\u093f\u0915 \u092a\u0938\u0940\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u0947 \u092c\u091a\u093e\u0935 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u092f\u094b\u0917\u093f\u0915 \u0918\u092e\u094c\u0930\u0940 \u0928\u093e\u0936\u0915 \u092a\u093e\u0909\u0921\u0930 \u0915\u0947 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092f\u094b\u0917 \u0915\u093f\u092f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092c\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option2": "\u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092c\u094b\u0928\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option3": "\u0938\u0932\u094d\u092b\u094d\u092f\u0942\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option4": "\u092b\u0949\u0938\u094d\u092b\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "Answer": "\u092c\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932"}, {"Date": "2020-07-24 08:46:47+00:00", "question": "[2/30] \u0917\u0930\u094d\u092e\u093f\u092f\u094b\u0902 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0905\u0924\u094d\u092f\u0927\u093f\u0915 \u092a\u0938\u0940\u0928\u0947 \u0938\u0947 \u092c\u091a\u093e\u0935 \u0915\u0947 \u0932\u093f\u090f \u0928\u093f\u092e\u094d\u0928 \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u0938\u0947 \u0915\u094c\u0928 \u0938\u093e \u092f\u094b\u0917\u093f\u0915 \u0918\u092e\u094c\u0930\u0940 \u0928\u093e\u0936\u0915 \u092a\u093e\u0909\u0921\u0930 \u0915\u0947 \u0930\u0942\u092a \u092e\u0947\u0902 \u092a\u094d\u0930\u092f\u094b\u0917 \u0915\u093f\u092f\u093e \u091c\u093e\u0924\u093e \u0939\u0948?", "option1": "\u092c\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option2": "\u0915\u093e\u0930\u094d\u092c\u094b\u0928\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option3": "\u0938\u0932\u094d\u092b\u094d\u092f\u0942\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "option4": "\u092b\u0949\u0938\u094d\u092b\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "Answer": "\u092c\u094b\u0930\u093f\u0915 \u0905\u092e\u094d\u0932", "This quiz channel use quiz bot :-": 87}]